<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SAnToS Open PCA Pump Artifacts</title>
    <link>https://openpcapump.santoslab.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SAnToS Open PCA Pump Artifacts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://openpcapump.santoslab.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://openpcapump.santoslab.org/artifacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openpcapump.santoslab.org/artifacts/</guid>
      <description>Artifacts A primary goal of the Open PCA Pump project is to provide realistic system development that are aligned and provide traceability across the development cycle.
Several important artifacts (in particular the presentation of use cases and requirements) were inspired by the FAA Requirements Engineering Management Handbook (REMH).
The following artifacts are currently available.
System Overview and Operational Concepts The System Overview provides an high-level description of the pump device, its medical purpose, the care-giving context into which it is deployed, and its interactions with people and equipment in the context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://openpcapump.santoslab.org/lectures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openpcapump.santoslab.org/lectures/</guid>
      <description>Lectures Lecture slides are available to support the use of the Open PCA Pump Artifacts in teaching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://openpcapump.santoslab.org/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openpcapump.santoslab.org/overview/</guid>
      <description>Overview The SAnToS Lab Open PCA Pump Artifacts provide an end-to-end example of model-based development (with integrated formal methods) of the software for an &amp;ldquo;at scale&amp;rdquo; medical device.
The artifacts were developed in cooperation with US FDA and medical device industry engineers to illustrate best practices in rigorous engineering for medical devices.
The artifacts include operational concepts (formal use cases), requirements, formal architecture models, formal behavioral contracts in models and code, testing and formal verification, and an assurance case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://openpcapump.santoslab.org/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openpcapump.santoslab.org/resources/</guid>
      <description>Resources This page provides links to resources that may be helpful in understanding the use of PCA pumps in clinical settings, PCA pump features, and safety issues.
Clinical Training Videos for PCA Pumps Clinical training videos form Columbia Gorge Community College
PCA Introduction (video) PCA Setup I (video) PCA Setup II [(video)] (http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kXaMW754Hk4) PCA Initiation (video) PCA Manage I (video) PCA Manage II (video) PCA overview from hunterrobert2004 Youtube channel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://openpcapump.santoslab.org/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://openpcapump.santoslab.org/tools/</guid>
      <description>Tools The Open PCA Pump Artifacts make use of the following tools.
BLESS
Sireum
Sireum is a programming language, software engineering, and formal methods framework developed at Kansas State University. This class will use Slang (the Sireum programming Language) and Logika (an automated SMT-based verification environment for Slang)
Download and installation instructions &amp;ndash; installation based on git sources is recommended Video overview of Slang and Logika </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
